I'm going to crush his spirit, his will to fight, to stand, and to resist.
I'll make him see, I'll prove to him that all his hard work and confidence mean absolutely nothing.
You can't attack me anyway.
Not only a human in my corner so that he is born.
If you get started or not, the dream will remember her score ever.
You can smile again
太陽浴びて
You can fly away
世界は君の輝きを待ってる
大地を踏みしめて
君は目覚めてゆく
天使の微笑みで
連れ出して
始まりはいつでも
細くないさ
何度でも立ち上がれ
期待して
独卟 Hawk
地域の敵に
一番に
近くvoll転ばせました
でも進む Ganon
Hmm, Gyo, huh?
The moment I grasped his arm, he focused his aura there to block my attack.
You fool! You think you've figured me out now, don't you?
Oh, what's the matter? That was just a simple body blow.
If you focus your aura wherever I grab you, then you leave yourself open everywhere else.
Pointless. In fact, it was worse than pointless. It even backfired on you.
It's just like Bisky said.
You won't be smiling much longer.
One more, and you're finished.
Impossible. That was the hardest hit so far. He shouldn't have been able to counter.
But he did, and that means that he kept the damage to a minimum.
In other words, he blocked me with standard defenses, not by relying on aura.
Did he just guess that I wouldn't set off an explosion?
No. That look!
So hey, Bisky, how come Genthrou doesn't get burned by his own explosions?
Oh, it's pretty simple, actually.
You see, he covers his hand with more aura than he uses to detonate.
Oh, I get it.
It's a technique that requires quite a large reserve of aura.
Now's as good a time as any.
Let's see if you can tell, huh?
Excellent reaction.
You've almost perfected Gyo.
All right, now one more time.
Huh?
You could tell the difference?
Yeah. You used less aura the second time, didn't you?
Yes, that's right. You pass.
Now that you can tell the difference, you're going to have a much easier time facing him.
Right before Genthrou uses his little flower, he'll use Gyo on his hand.
But when he's pretending to use his ability, he's going to attack you somewhere else and won't bother using Gyo.
Huh.
If you can feel whether the hand touching you is protected by Gyo or not, that means you'll be able to thwart his attacks and feints to some extent.
I see. You knew from my Gyo. Very clever.
Like I said before, the shallow strategy you're using, it's going to backfire.
If my little flower catches you when you're not using enough aura to defend yourself, a hit to the face will blow your eyes, your nose, and your mouth clean away.
A hit to the arms or legs will incinerate your skin, severely damaging any nerves or muscle. You'll have no fingers or toes left.
It's impossible for you to guard against all of my Gyo attacks with your Gyo.
So now what? I've no interest in continuing this. This fight has shown me something.
You have talent as well as a promising future, filled with opportunities. Don't you think that throwing it all away just for the sake of pride is meaningless?
Come on, brat. Give up already.
If he shows signs that he's going to use both hands to blow you up, that's a red flag. And you must focus on following the plan exactly.
Biscuit, Killua, I'm sorry. I know it's selfish of me, but I've got to go with my gut. I have to try. Because... I just had a great idea.
Well, if you really feel that way, then just give up, Ganthru!
How unfortunate.
Let me show you that there are some fates even worse than dying. I'll give you an example.
First, I'll blow up both of your arms. Use Gyo to protect the one you want to keep. And after that's done, I'll blow up your remaining arm along with your left leg.
Again, use Gyo to protect the one you want to keep. We'll continue in that fashion until you're out of limbs.
Yeah, we'll just go ahead and try.
All right.
Take this!
What... what just happened?
Blood... I'm injured? Was I attacked?
Show me Rock!
Crap!
Move! Get out of the way!
John... Ken...
Rock!
Did he hit me? No. I just tripped.
What the hell was that? What happened?
Wait. Now I get it. This little brat sacrificed both hands!
But it seems the damage wasn't distributed evenly. He probably gave up on his left hand. He protected his right with 30% of his aura, and focused the remaining 70% in his legs to attack me!
I use Aura to blow up targets as well as to shield my hand from the blast. But if I attack with both hands, it leaves the rest of my body defenseless. He took advantage of that. Still, no sane person would ever actually try it!
At least, I gave him a pretty good scare.
This hurts so bad, I feel like I'm gonna die! But... I'm going for it!
That's... enough.
Wait. Is he giving up?
Of course. It all makes sense. He's lost his left hand, and his right is badly injured. He did manage to land a hit on me. Perhaps that satisfied him.
Okay, I'm done being selfish now. Time to get serious! Come on, and fight me!
What is wrong with this brat? He's completely insane!
Book!
A card? He shouldn't have anything I need to worry about.
Wait, it transformed? Paladin's necklace? What is he planning?
This is your last chance to surrender. Once I use this, you could die. So think about it carefully.
It's obvious that you're bluffing. But wait. This is my chance. Book.
I give up. You're never going to admit defeat. That much is clear.
Take what you want.
I'll silence him. Crushing his windpipe and knocking him out would be best. Then I can take the cards from his binder.
But I do have one request. What?
I only ask that you leave me this card right here.
He blocked my second attack with Gyo!
But at least I managed to crush his throat, which means he won't be able to save Book or Gain anymore!
Gain through! That's the worst decision you could have possibly made!
One minute!
That smell!
He can't use this little flower anymore! I'm gonna take him down!
Book!
Oh, I see. This is gasoline. That's a good one.
It's true that I can't use little flower now. However, I have another ability. Countdown.
You may recall that I can set a bomb on someone, and all I have to do is touch them and say the word bomber.
And if you intend to disarm it, then your only recourse would be to touch me while saying I caught the bomber.
This one is ten times stronger than little flower, so you won't be able to block it with Nen.
All of the activation requirements have been met. If I touch you and say bomber, the countdown will begin.
I'd run if I were you. Well, if you still have the strength.
Oh, yeah. My requirements have been met, too!
Now show me, Rock!
His earlier attack... I can't get too close. Is he keeping me back?
John... Gen... Rock!
A pit trap! But why? He's falling, too!
It's deep. Far too deep to climb out. Still, he's in the same position. Doesn't he see that he's cornered himself?
He's gone!
Genthru...
If a card is removed from the binder for a minute, it reverts to an item!
A rock!
G scheduled for 1998, it isn't a insane neutraláb tanto at once.
I don't know why, huh?
Is it in an animal park?
Show me... Rock.
Jan... Get...
No, wait! Hold on, I surrender! I surrender!
Rock!
You're awake?
Hurry and get your binder out.
That's right.
We want you to return all the cards you stole from the people you betrayed.
On one condition.
Use Angel's breath to heal Bara of his injuries.
We have a clone card.
Don't worry about it.
That was always a part of the plan.
We already prepared six copies of clone for just such an occasion.
Book.
Game!
What manner of aid do you wish of me?
We need you to heal his throat.
And while you're at it, both of his hands, too.
Scratch that.
Just fix everything wrong with him.
That is a simple task.
And so I shall restore his body to its former state.
Yes!
I'm healed!
Now, fare thee well.
Right.
Here it is.
The extra Angel's breath card.
Gain!
Next up is Killua.
Okay, Gunthru.
We're going to use your binder now.
Do as you please.
And clone on.
Attention.
Angel's breath has reached its maximum card limit.
The clone will be destroyed.
Hey, wait a minute!
What just happened?
Did I mess it all up?
No.
It's Gorenu.
He used either clone or transform to increase the number of Angel's breath vouchers.
Two of his vouchers became Angel's breath.
That must be why.
Attention.
Another player has used contact to reach you.
Hey, it's Gorenu.
Looks like you did it, huh?
But I don't approve.
If you use Angel's breath to heal these murderers, then the trade is off.
Could I use it?
Yeah, of course.
But I'm an assassin.
Huh?
Sure they've killed.
I've killed more.
Every player in this game risks their life in one way or another.
That doesn't mean it's okay to kill people.
But all the people I killed weren't nearly as ready to die as the ones these guys did.
I'm way worse than they could ever be.
You're wrong.
You're not at all like them.
I mean, I like you, but these guys?
I hate their guts.
Yeah, that isn't very logical.
Oh, forget logic.
It's how I feel.
Don't you feel the same way?
But it's not our place to judge.
We don't think it's right to let them die just because we hate them.
Both sides risk their lives in battle.
And both are prepared to kill if necessary.
But when the fight's over, well, those rules cease to apply.
I still haven't forgiven Genthru for killing all those other players.
Not yet, at least.
But before the fight even started, the three of us agreed.
We'd bring six clone cards with us just in case.
I don't really remember why we decided that, but I do know one thing.
It wasn't based on logic or reason.
It just made sense to all of us.
Once the fight was over and we'd obtain the Angel's Breath card, we would use it on whoever was hurt.
We made the decision together, so we wanted to stick to it.
But I get how you feel, Mr. Gerenu.
I guess it can't be helped.
Sorry, Killua.
Could you wait a little longer?
Not a problem.
My hands will eventually heal on their own.
Things have changed, so we can't use clone anymore.
And there's just one Angel's Breath left.
Hang on.
Only one?
Are you talking about the original card?
I want you to use it on Genthru.
I'm gonna be alright.
Let's use a company to go to Masadora.
Yeah.
Hey, wait up!
Alright, you can have Angel's Breath.
Whatever you guys want.
Really?
You're sure?
Well, to be honest, even before you told me everything, I decided to give it to you.
And not just Angel's Breath, but all the cards that we gathered in the game.
We all agreed.
Tezgera, his team, and me.
Thing is, we all decided to quit the game.
Oh, wow.
I'm all better.
So, Mr. Batera...
Yeah.
He paid off Team Tezgera for breaking the contract.
I settled for four billion Jenny.
Wait, four billion?
You want to put something on over?
No!
Hey, what are you talking about?
Of course you get some.
We each get a billion.
Huh?
It's only fair.
I could never have done this on my own.
It was only possible because we all teamed up and worked together.
I can't believe that I'm here!
You're a really nice guy!
Has anyone ever told you that?
Anyway, you can take all the cards.
They're yours.
But there is one condition.
You must be the first players to complete the game.
Piece of cake.
You've got 99 specified slot cards.
That means all you need now is number zero.
One more card to go.
Oh, yeah.
97.
98.
And this one makes...
99!
This announcement is for all players.
One of your fellow competitors has just collected 99 specified slot cards.
So in honor of this accomplishment, 10 minutes from now, we'll hold an island-wide quiz contest.
You are all welcome to participate if you so choose.
There will be 100 total questions that deal with the specified slot cards.
Whichever player is able to answer the most questions correctly will receive number zero, Ruler's Blessing, as a prize.
Please stand by with your binders open and ready.
All the questions are about the specified slot cards?
I get it.
I bet the questions are designed so that players who mainly stole their cards can't answer them.
Someone's coming!
Wait!
There are more!
The battle has been long and grueling, but now it's reached the final stage.
Ensuite!
Next!
More than a elegance.
Will there be a voice that makes it as we begin to?
That's why I didn't want to move.
Love takes a bite,
every breath lasts in.
Time to lose forever.
Pay to next.
And clip the night as Light became.
We've stayed with fake tears that are overcome.
I'll keep this journey.
向かい風としていながら それでも進む理由がある
だから友よ 置いてくためだけに生きるのはまだ 早いだろ
身につけたもの 抱え込んだもの 手放したとき 始まる何か
上手く生きてく レシピを破り捨てて 感じるリズム
そう僕らのやり方で
Coming up! The Great Island Tutorial!